<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>JMW</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on JMW</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Jun 2020 10:31:47 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Reflections on some advice about comparisons</title>
      <link>/reflections_on_advice/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jun 2020 10:31:47 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/reflections_on_advice/</guid>
      <description>May 2020 was a rollercoaster of a month, with my struggles (and triumphs) in productivity driving most of the variation in my mood, self-esteem, ability to be supportive of others, etc. Now, after a full week of having recovered from feeling under the weather, it is Monday morning of a new week, it&amp;rsquo;s the first day of a new month, and it feels like a good opportunity to try to parse a few of the scattered thoughts I&amp;rsquo;ve had in the past few weeks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My writing</title>
      <link>/writing/writing_landing_page/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2020 20:44:47 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/writing/writing_landing_page/</guid>
      <description>Writing here</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unemployment is up 3200%, and this is not a recession</title>
      <link>/writing/not_a_recession_yet/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 10:41:46 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/writing/not_a_recession_yet/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s true that unemployment is skyrocketing. The painful anecdotes behind the terrifying numbers are somber reminders of how an economy operating at half-capacity disproportionately burdens our most vulnerable populations. However, the debate around COVID-19 public health and financial policies has stagnated in the face of a false dichotomy - succinctly characterized by the trending phrase - &amp;ldquo;GDP or Grandma&amp;rdquo;.
Many have voiced their opposition to this facetious &amp;ldquo;debate&amp;rdquo; (links below to some I&amp;rsquo;ve come across).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Art landing page</title>
      <link>/art/art_landing_page/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2020 11:12:11 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/art/art_landing_page/</guid>
      <description>ART HERE GET YOUR ART HERE Art art</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Hello! I am Jenny, currently based in San Francisco.
Interested in economics, reading, meditation and mindfulness practice, baking cakes, frisbee, public transit (and other urban issues), and sometimes writing.
Here is a place to collect various reading, writing, and other thoughts - an exercise in sharing, collecting, and learning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recent reading</title>
      <link>/reading/reading_landing_page/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/reading/reading_landing_page/</guid>
      <description> Books  The Source of Self-Regard - Toni Morrison (current) Normal People - Sally Rooney Sing, Unburied, Sing - Jesmyn Ward The Art of Learning - Josh Waitzkin  Articles  The Productive Career of Robert Solow - Peter Dizikes, MIT Review The Lingering of Loss - Jill Lepore, The New Yorker  Papers  Does Working from Home Work - Bloom et al 2015, QJE Differences in Differences with Variation in Treatment Timing - Goodman-Bacon 2019  More  Goodreads Online reading &amp;amp; quotes  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>